socialengineaddons.com 2016-02-01

# Privacy Policy | SocialEngineAddOns

SocialEngineAddOns respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protect it in all respects.

The information about the user as collected by SocialEngineAddOns is: (a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation. You can rest assured that all information entered by you for your identification will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. We will not share, lease or sell your personal information to third parties.

To avail certain services on our website, users are required to provide certain information for the registration and checkout processes namely:-

  1. A )  Email
  2. B )  First Name and Last Name
  3. C )  Company
  4. D )  Phone Number

The Information as supplied by the users enables us to:

 \- improve our site, services and provide you the most user-friendly experience.

 \- maintain internal records.

To improve the responsiveness of the site for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally.

SocialEngineAddOns includes links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

All information gathered on SocialEngineAddOns is securely stored within the SocialEngineAddOns controlled database. Access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

In case you believe any of your information with us is incorrect, please contact us and we will promptly rectify any incorrect information.
